

YVETTE TANILA

JUNIOR DEVELOPER

PERSONAL PROFILE

Results-driven Junior Web Developer, with previous senior experience in accounting. I believe nothing is impossible to achieve and I have demonstrated learning how to code in 6 months with Strive School. Curious, innovation enthusiast, fast-thinker, and pace-setter, I enjoy tackling challenges, more than anything when they give me the opportunity to step

SKILLS

- Html & Css
- Bootstrap
- Javascript
- React.is (Hooks & Redux)
- Node.js
- MongoDB
- PostgreSQL
- Express
- Typescript
- Cloud Technologies

CONTACT

- ¶ Umeå, Sweden
- /yvette809
- nchombuayvta@gmail.com
- +46760726885
- in /yvette-tanila

EDUCATION

Strive School

MERN Stack Development | Apr 20 - Oct 20

Strive School is a 6 months program designed to train talents with STEM or different Backgrounds as Web Developer.

Umeå Univesity

Masters in Business Development & Internationalisation | 2010 - 2012

In this program, I learnt more on business strategies, entrepreneurship most importantly on the strategies SMEs use for internationalisation. I also studied some accounting and finance courses; advanced financial accounting, financial statement analysis and evaluation, corporate governance etc.

Univesity of Buea

B.sc Accounting | 2004 - 2007

I had the opportunity to carry out a research on the factors investors consider before carrying on an investment. This project was done with the help of my acquired knowledge on cost analysis, risk evaluation and forecasting etc.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Accountant

NXT Tax Consultancy | Jun 2014 - aug 2019

- Tax filing and declaration
- Preparation of financial Statements
- Budget computation and Analysis
- Bank Reconcilation

Accountant

Mukete Estates Itd | May 2007 - Jan 2010

- Payroll Accounting
- Financial Statement preparation
- Cost Analysis, Account Receivables, Payables

PROJECTS

WSK WEBPAGE

This is a project to showcase the activities of my sports club and provide the players an opportunity to connect with one another through posting, comments and so on. Here, the players have the opportunity to register a profile which can be visible to potential investors.

ELECTROSHOP

This is a website that sells electronic products

GITHUB FINDER

This is a small project to showcase github profiles of developers and see their recent projects, followers and so on

TECHNOLOGIES USED

CSS / BOOTSTRAP /REACT HOOKS AND REDUX / NODE.JS /EXPRESS.JS /MONGODB

Repo Link

https://github.com/yvette809/wakanda-frontendhttps://github.com/yvette809/Wakanda-backend

Webpage Link

https://wakanda-client.herokuapp.com/

TECHNOLOGIES USED

CSS / BOOTSTRAP / REACT HOOKS AND REDUX / NODE.JS / EXPRESS.JS / MONGODB

REPO LINK

https://github.com/yvette809/e-commerce/tree/master

Webpage Link

https://electroshop1.herokuapp.com/

TECHNOLOGIES USED

CSS / BOOTSTRAP / REACT

Repo Link

https://github.com/yvette809/Githubfinder

Webpage Link

To be published...